

SUMMARY

7+ years experienced *Technical Artist*. Who worked on production on multi-disciplenary parts of game development process such as game development, shader creation, 3D game asset creation. Worked on multiple projects such as AR/VR game & applications, PC games & mobile games. Developed & published 2 mobile hit games in last 2 years.

SKILLS

Unity, C#, HLSL & Lighting, 3D Asset & Animation Creation, Graphic Design, Game Design, Level Design, Project Management.





OGULCAN KARAOGLU

TECHNICAL ARTIST

CONTACT

+905530470213

oulcankaraolu@gmail.com

5777 St. No : 49 Izmir/Turkey 35110

EDUCATION

Information Technologies

2011 - 2015

HIGH SCHOOL DEGREE
ITO FOUNDATION SULEYMAN TASTEKIN
TECHNICAL HIGH SCHOOL

DEMO REEL

Video Link



WORK EXPERIENCE

TECHNICAL ARTIST

FUNRIKA GAMES // 2022-Present

- -Shader Creation in Unity.
- -Scene Creation in Unity.
- -Lighting.
- -Optimisation.
- -Animation.

GAME DEVELOPER / TECHNICAL ARTIST

UNLIT GAMES // 2020-2022

- -Prototyping Creation in Unity(C#)
- -Leading the studio to create Hyper-Casual games.
- -Shader Creation in Unity.
- -Game Design & Level Design
- -Game Art
- -Published 2 Hit Games Bridal Rush! PuppetMaster 3D
- -Game Portfolio Video

TECHNICAL ARTIST

MC Games Studio// 2019-2020

- -Prop, Environment, Character Modeling & Texturing
- -Level Design&Lighting in Unity.
- $\hbox{-Rigging\&Animation}.$
- -Shader Creation in Unity.
- -Building bridge between 3D Artists and Programmers for the project.

TECHNICAL ARTIST

PANDORA REALITY AR&VR SOLUTIONS // 2016-2019

- -3D Modeling&Texturing,
- -Shader Creation in Unity
- -Level Design&Lighting in Unreal and Unity.
- -Basic Rigging&Animation.
- -Tool developing for Artists in Unity.
- -Building bridge between 3D Artists and Programmers for the project.

SOLO PROJECTS

Drunken Fight Simulator - Steam

Synth Ninja - Steam

Jeff The Killer: Horror Sleep 1 & 2 - GPlay